const myQuestions = [
    {
      question: "Windows is a(n) ________ created by Microsoft.?",
      answers: {
        a: "operating system",
        b: "web browser",
        c: "word processor",
        d: "computer"
      },
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "The main workspace of a Windows computer is called the ________.?",
      answers: {
        a: "folder",
        b: "desktop",
        c: "shortcut",
        d: "taskbar"
      },
      correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
      question: "The icon that is yellowish in color is called ________.?",
      answers: {
        a: "shortcut",
        b: "file",
        c: "folder",
        d: "document"
      },
      correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
      question: "Let's say you're having trouble locating a file on your computer. Which of the following are good places to look for the file?",
      answers: {
        a: "The screensaver",
        b: "The Recycle Bin",
        c: "Default folders like My Documents",
        d: "Search"
      },
      correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
      question: "If you want to move a window, you can click and drag the ________.?",
      answers: {
        a: "top of the window",
        b: "taskbar",
        c: "Close button",
        d: "Start button"
      },
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "Suppose you have several windows open on your desktop, but some of them are hidden behind other windows. What is the easiest way to switch to one of the hidden windows?",
      answers: {
        a: "Click the icon on the taskbar",
        b: "Press Ctrl+Alt+Delete on your keyboard",
        c: "Close all programs and reopen them one-by-one",
        d: "Press your computer's Power button"
      },
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      question:"True or False: When you move a file to the Recycle Bin, it will be immediately deleted from your computer.",
      answers: {
        a: "True",
        b: "False",
      },
      correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
      question:"When you double-click a file on the desktop, it will open in the ________.?",
      answers: {
        a: "Start menu",
        b: "most recently-opened application",
        c: "default application for that file type",
        d: "Control Panel"
      },
      correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
      question:"True or False: You can only have one user account on a Windows computer.",
      answers: {
        a: "True",
        b: "False"
      },
      correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
      question:"When would you use the Ctrl+Alt+Delete keyboard shortcut?",
      answers: {
        a: "When a program is unresponsive",
        b: "When you want to delete a file",
        c: "When a program first opens",
        d: "When you first boot up your computer"
      },
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
  ];
  

  export default myQuestions;